# Martin Goldszein

# **Web Designer**

48 years old Argentinian living in Colonia, Uruguay

(598 97531058) martin.goldszein@gmail.com

**Summary** 

A creative and experienced web designer with over 22 years of experience in the industry.

I am a passionate Frontend Developer specialized in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with a solid experience in WordPress and Shopify.

Dedicated to keeping up-to-date with the latest web design trends and techniques.

I have developed responsive and engaging user interfaces for clients in various industries.

I collaborated closely with the design and backend teams to ensure seamless integration.

As a professional with hearing impairment, I want to highlight that my ability to communicate in English, both in writing and reading, is fluent. Although I face challenges in online conversations, I have the support of my partner to ensure effective collaboration."

**Skills** 

Adobe Creative Suite

Figma

WordPress

WooCommerce

Shopify / Liquify

HTML / CSS

Javascript

PHP / MySQL

Accessibility Developer Tools

Validator W3

Validator.nu

WAI-ARIA

SEO

## **Experience**

#### Freelance

feb. 2008 - 2014 · 16 years

Programmer Senior XHTML / CSS / jQuery

**InTacto** 

feb. 2008 - 2011 · 3 years

Programmer Senior

XHTML/CSS and WordPress

**Bracket Media** 

oct. 2007 - nov. 2008 · 1 año 2 meses

Graphic Designer

**XAGA** 

nov. 2004 - sept. 2007  $\cdot$  2 años 11 meses

Frontend Development with HTML / CSS

Paginar.net

may. 2006 - mar. 2007 · 11 months

**Education** 

### Escuela técnica ORT

Graphic Designer 1996 - 1998

#### **Escuela Martin Buber**

Nivel Secundario